Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Bottoms up!
Tripp's back!
Alys!
Kei?
You little witch!
Let's go, Fier.
Have you seen Tripp?
Did you two fight?
We can't be together!
There is no us!
Are you dumb?
Who is Fier?
- Goodbye, Alys.
- Drake!
I thought we were just taking a break.
We never broke up, right?
Okay, Alys.
Let's break up.
I'm setting you free.
So, please let me go, as well.
Good morning, baby!
- Good morning, Mommy.
- Come, have a seat.
Let's eat breakfast.
Where's Dad?
Well,
your dad is at work.
And then your little brother
is studying.
So, do you have any plans for today?
Honestly,
I still have a headache
from all the thinking and
pondering I did last night.
Should I do what Tripp says?
Should I chase Drake?
Alys?
Did you stay up all night?
You look sleepy.
Sorry, Mom.
I have a lot going through
my head right now.
Like what?
I'm going on a vacation.
Oh, finally!
Well deserved!
Where are you headed to?
I don't know yet.
Maybe somewhere south.
Oh, good choice!
Okay.
Let's make a deal.
I'll pay for everything, okay?
Just enjoy and relax.
Alright?
Thank you, Mommy.
- You're the best!
- You're welcome!
Okay, let's eat!
I think I really need a vacation
to take my mind off things.
I think I really need this because
lately my mind had been
doing rash things to me.
Hello?
Hi, Bestie!
Aya!
Yes, Bestie, why did you call?
-What’s up?
-Uhm...
Where are you?
Your mom says you're going on a vacation.
Word travels fast!
I'm on the way to Batangas right now.
Why, Bestie?
Have you picked a place to stay?
Any ideas?
Uhm...
At the resort where Mommy usually
books for family vacations.
Why do you ask, Bestie?
Oh! Uhm...
Bestie, nothing.
Okay, uhm...
Enjoy! You deserve it!
Bestie? Bestie!
Hmm? What's Aya’s problem?
It's too early to be hyper.
Oh, well.
I'll just enjoy myself then.
Sun, sand and sea...
Here I come!
There were nights
that I just couldn't sleep.
It felt like torture.
Just lying there,
not being able to sleep at all.
How long should I be gone for?
I think one week should suffice.
After that, my mind should probably be
fresh enough not to screw things up.
I'll follow Tripp's advice.
Maybe I'll try to fix
things up with Drake.
No, not chase him back.
I just want to have
things back to normal.
Maybe Tripp was right.
I still love Drake.
I think I never stopped loving him.
He was my epic love.
But,
I don't want that kind of love.
I just want a quiet life.
Complications would never be my thing.
Hello, Ma'am.
Good morning.
Good morning, Sir.
Good morning, Ms. Perez.
Hi!
A welcome drink, Ma'am?
No, thanks.
Why is she calling?
Maybe she felt guilty?
But why would she?
It wasn't like...
Sorry, Kei.
Vacation mode.
On a vacation.
Look after Tripp for me, okay?
Thanks, Kei. XOXO
Hi, Ma'am!
Welcome to Layag Resort!
Hello!
How may I help you today?
I have a reservation under Alys Perez.
Alys Perez.
Okay, thank you Ma'am.
Hold on, I'll just check the
details on the reservation.
Ma'am, here's your key!
- Thank —
- Ah!
By the way, Ma'am,
we have accomodated the changes
made to the booking earlier.
Changes?
Yes, Ma'am. Changes.
Actually, someone called earlier
to upgrade your room from
lower villa to upper villa!
For a better view.
Huh? I'm sorry?
Actually, Ma'am,
the same card was used for
the adjustment of your room, yes.
Oh yeah, that's Mom's card.
She must've upgraded my room!
Oh, that's so sweet of her!
She really knows I need this vacation.
Okay, thank you.
If you're ready and
everything is settled then,
we will escort you to your room.
Okay.
Just hold on.
Drake?!
What is Drake doing here?!
Oh my god!
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Here’s your welcome drink.
Thank you.
Hello, Mommy?
Hi, Bestie!
Aya?!
Yes, Bestie!
The one and only.
Why do you have Mommy's phone?
She says she doesn't
want to talk to you.
How come?
Do you know why my room
upgraded to an upper villa?
And do you have an idea
why Drake is here?
Don't you remember, Bestie?
I'm #TeamDralys for life.
You're both grownups.
Make love, not war.
Oh my god, Aya! What the hell?!
Just stay there.
Don't be such a killjoy, okay?
Damn it, Aya. You're so crazy!
What are you trying to pull now, huh?
No, Bestie,
I'm not crazy.
I'm your best friend, okay?
So sit back and relax.
And if nothing happens over the week,
I shall never talk about Drake
ever again.
Promise.
Even if it'll hurt my heart.
I'll shift to #TeamTrippZy instead.
Damn it, Aya. You're insane!
You're welcome, Bestie.
Love you. Enjoy!
Make love, not war.
Hello? Hello!
Aya, that little witch!
What's her deal?
Why is she so into this kind of thrill?
Okay, Alys.
In yoga, they tell you to
take three deep breaths.
Okay, Alys. Aja!
Hi!
Hi?
What are you doing here?
Dad.
Gosh, he's back to his
one-word utterances.
So Drake Palma.
Excuse me, can I change rooms?
The upper villas are too big for me.
Actually, Ma'am, all rooms are occupied.
I’m sorry.
Seriously?
I don't see any other guests here.
Uh...
Actually, Ma’am, all rooms are paid for
under the name of Ms...
Dana Guzman.
Shit, Aya.
I understand but my mom's
not even here so...
Yes, Ma'am. But unfortunately,
we cannot change the booking.
Because the rooms are paid
for under a different name.
But, the good thing is
the upper villa is still
available for the two of you!
Perfect.
Take the room.
I’ll just leave.
Me too. I'm not in the mood
for a vacation anymore.
Aya!
And what are you smiling about?
Nothing.
Fine!
Okay, Ma'am. Have a nice day!
Enjoy your stay!
Love, love, love!
Tss.
My phone is useless. My car is useless.
Share a room?
As you can see, the resort
has plenty of space!
This place is a perfect place.
To relax, enjoy...
and be in love!
With the nature, of course.
On the left side is the tranquil sea,
with it's wide shore
where you can chase
each other's feelings.
I mean, you two could chase
each other along the shore.
This place is magical!
Like you two.
Ahh!
Finally!
This is your villa!
As mentioned earlier, the two of
you will stay on the upper villa.
For a romantic, intimate
and better view.
So, follow me and
I'm sure you'll love this.
I'm so excited for your stay here.
And look at the view!
You can see the vast ocean.
You can hang out there at night.
Follow me.
Okay guys, just follow me.
Be careful with the luggages.
Let's go!
Ms. Perez and Mr. Palma,
this is your beautiful
and intimate villa!
Are you sure that there aren't
any other villas available?
Yes, Ma'am.
Like I said, we're fully booked
right now.
This the only one available.
Fully booked?
But it was my mom
who booked the rooms.
And you don't have
any other guests here.
This is the only available
villa and room, Ma'am.
It's nice here!
Okay.
I guess this is my room.
Ma'am, sorry.
This room is not available.
The keys for the lock are missing.
- Are you sure?
- Uh, yes, Ma'am.
Ms. Perez,
Mr. Palma,
follow me.
Follow me.
This is your beautiful room.
This room comes with air condition,
a flatscreen TV and free WiFi.
And through that door is the bathroom
where basic toiletries are provided
and fresh towels.
Not only that,
the best thing about this room is...
is the best view of the beach.
It's so romantic!
Makes you fall in love, right?
So, Ms. Perez,
Mr. Palma, I'll go ahead.
Again...
Love, love, love!
Enjoy your stay!
I am so going to kill you, Aya!
One room, one bed?
You take the bed.
Drake.
I know you're not comfortable
sleeping on the couch.
You’re like a prince in your home.
Uncle Steve doesn’t even
make you do anything,
and you expect me to
let you sleep there?
So, what?
You expect me to let you sleep here?
Uhm...
We can...
We can share a bed —
No!
No, but —
Alys!
I'm a man.
And I'm still
in love with you.
So don't dare me.
Can I use your bathroom?
I’ll just have a quick shower.
Hmm.
Thank you.
It's better for him to stay
here instead of the couch.
It's more comfortable here.
He’s taking so long to take a bath.
Oh no.
I might see his body
when he comes out after showering.
I need a distraction.
Ahh!
Oh my god!
Why are they all adult channels?
- What?
- Oh, god!
Oh my god!
Don't startle me, Alys!
You’re the one who startled me!
You didn’t say you were finished
taking a shower!
Oh, yeah.
It's your turn.
Okay.
Are you done?
I'm done.
Are you sure?
Okay.
It seems nice to take a
walk along the shore.
How did we end up like this?
We used to be so comfortable
around each other.
To the point where I was even
able to touch his underwear.
But now,
I can't even look him in the eye.
Funny how things work, right?
Alys.
Drake, uhm...
Alys, would you...
Huh?
Would you
treat me the same way
you did before?
You've been acting so cringe lately.
Sure.
He really did love me.
I hope...
I hope he finds someone he can love.
Not me but,
someone who's worthy of him.
Drake is a fine man.
Any girl would be lucky to have him.
Uh...
Do you want to go for a walk?
Drake!
Hey, Drake, wait for me!
Hey!
Drake, wait for me.
Oh, geez!
Why are you laughing?
Was that funny?
This.
Us.
It's like we're in high school
all over again.
Huh?
Alys?
Hmm?
Can we go back to how
we were in high school?
But...
It’s because —
High school is my fondest memory.
Because in high school,
I had you.
But —
So on this day
and the next few days
that we’ll be here at this resort,
can we go back to how things
were in high school?
Can you make me feel like
we're back in high school again?
After that, you can go back
to your reality, Alys.
What about your reality?
My reality sucks.
How come?
You have Cristine.
And... Fier.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Nothing.
Never mind.
Alys, don't force it
if you can't say it.
Huh?
My reality sucks.
Because you're no longer with me.
So, Alys...
Can you give me this one vacation?
But, Tripp...
I really did care about Tripp.
Unlike what he believed in,
he was my priority.
I think about him
before I make decisions.
Well, most of the time.
Just one week.
Wouldn't that be selfish?
Selfish?
All my life, Alys,
I've been the one giving.
Making sacrifices.
Can I be selfish just this once?
I don't know what to say anymore.
This is Drake Palma talking to me.
And he is practically begging.
Who am I to refuse
what he’s asking for?
Drake?
What?
I'll be your fairy godmother.
And we'll go back to the time
when we first met!
Boom!
We're back in SCA!
Hi, Drakey Baby!
God, he smiled!
And not a little, forced smile, okay.
He freaking smiled!
Bird brain! Always a noob.
You're a meanie. Such a meanie!
Let’s go on a date.
Only if you’re treating me.
This beach is beautiful.
I missed you so much.
Me too, Drakey Baby.
Ahh!
What happened?
Oh my god!
That's a lot of blood.
Hey!
What happened to you?
Geez.
Relax, it's just a cut.
Seeing blood just makes me nauseous.
My classmate in Paris,
he cut his finger.
And now, everytime I see blood
I throw up.
It's okay, Alys.
Even if it's bloody, just don't look.
Are you okay now?
Drake?
What's his problem?
Hey, Drake!
What's your problem?
I thought we were all good?
I thought we had a truce?
A ceasefire?
What is it now?
Hey, Drake!
Are you really not going to answer —
Are you pregnant?
Huh?
What?
What the hell, Drake?
You're going to ask me that
and then turn your back on me?
Are you crazy?
Listen, Drake Sebastian
Jimenez Palma.
What?
So what if I am pregnant?
Don't ask me a question if you're
not ready for the answer.
I feel like I'm challenging the devil.
The thrill is enveloping my very soul.
It's like playing with fire.
Something you know is dangerous,
yet you still want it.
I don't care who
that child's father is
as long as you're the mother.
I've stopped caring
about everything, Alys.
I only care about you.
You're the only one I want.
And everything else is just a bonus.
Drake...
So?
You're really pregnant.
I’m not.
Drake...
Living abroad for five years?
Sleeping around has
always been an option.
All my classmates did it but
that's just really not me.
Thank you.
Why? For what?
For this.
This.
And this.
You're so sappy,
it's getting annoying!
That's not you.
Let's go. It's getting late.
You're so sappy!
Drakey Baby, I’m hungry.
It’s really quiet here
at the resort, isn’t it?
You can’t see anything,
but I can hear something, Alys.
Huh?
Hearing what?
I don't hear anything but the waves.
Shh!
There are voices.
Can’t you hear them?
Voices?
Damn it, Drake!
I can't hear anything!
What voices?
That's it.
I'm calling mom and Aya.
Why would they book me here?
- Ahh!
Oh my god!
You're such a noob!
Argh!
You're such an idiot!
Why are you scaring me?
Don't scare me like that.
Give that to me!
I don't know what to do with you.
I'm ordering food.
Get it yourself.
I'm ordering food!
Go get it.
Come on!
There’s no wifi.
I’ll just call instead.
We’re sorry.
Your call cannot be completed.
There's no reception.
I’ll just go down.
Never mind.
I don’t want to go down alone.
I might end up seeing something else.
I thought you were hungry?
I'm fine.
I'll sleep it off.
My feet hurt.
We walked a long way earlier.
What are you doing?
Sit.
You know,
you've always had weak legs
since high school.
Better?
Noob.
Hmm?
What?
Please let me sleep. I'm so tired.
Noob.
Drake, please, I'm sorry.
My sleepiness is winning
over you right now.
Please.
Let's eat.
Let's go eat.
Get up.
You're getting up.
Eat.
What's all this?
Food.
I know it's food, Drake.
But why is there so much?
Alys,
I'm not letting you go hungry.
There.
Make yourself happy.
What do you want?
Surprise me.
I know this one's your favorite.
Oh!
Wait, that's too much!
You need to get fat.
I don't want to!
Why?
I worked hard for this
figure, you know?
You look like a stick.
Huh?!
I could draw you right
now using stick figures.
You're mean.
You're a bad person, Drake.
Drink.
Stop staring.
I can't help it.
Seriously, Sebastian?
I'm not going anywhere!
I can't eat when you
stare at me like that.
I won't run away. So, chill!
You should eat too.
You always say that you won't.
But I always find myself chasing you.
I won't run away, Drake.
Not now, not today.
Not tomorrow.
I'm all yours this week.
And then, what happens next?
Drake...
Will you please stop thinking
and just let things happen?
Happy endings aren't always
the best part of the story.
It's the chase.
It's the memories.
It's the fun!
Those are the
best parts of the story.
Alys?
Hmm?
I'm okay with you
making me chase after you.
As long as you're my end game.
Go eat.
You eat.
You've barely touched anything.
Uhm...
Alys, can I ask you something?
Hmm.
What do you want to know?
Have you ever considered
marrying me?
Yes.
That was the option, right?
That was the plan—
- Was?
- And the...
Fine.
Is.
I don't know, it's really confusing.
It's so weird!
It feels like we’re back
in high school again.
So, how's your heart doing, Bestie?
Don't tell me it was nothing.
It's nothing.
Cross your heart?
Swear it on your dying skin cells?
What should I be feeling?
I don't know.
Every time he looks at me, it's like...
nothing ever broke.
Like nothing ever happened.
Oh.
So there is something.
Fine!
I'm mad.
Just mad?
I know you, Bestie.
Fine.
I felt a little flutter.
Damn it.
I don't know why do I have to
feel this way again with him.
Bestie, he was never
gone in the first place.
And knowing Drake,
you know that's just how he is.
It's Drake.
He can't help but make
you feel things again.
That's what I'm afraid of, Bestie.
What if...
What if he still wants me but
I don't deserve him?
Bestie...
That's for Drake to decide, not you.
If he wants you,
he wants you.
Period.
Seriously?
You actually slept on the couch?
Good night, Drake.
Good night, Drakey Baby.
Good morning!
What's that?
Breakfast in bed.
Wow, it's like we're newly weds.
It's just practice.
Confident?
Of course.
I know he just ordered this,
but it still makes me happy.
Gestures like these would never
fail to make a girl smile.
A timeless act, in fact.
You've fallen for me, Alys.
And you’ll still end up falling for me.
It's inevitable.
Whatever you say, Palma.
OMG, what's this?
Is this mine?
Girls and their jewelries.
Boys and their toys.
Those are all for you.
Are you serious?
I never cheated on you.
Then why are you laughing?
I'm just grateful.
To hold your hand again.
To be able to speak to you.
It feels like home, Alys.
He's never this vocal
about his feelings for me.
I'm not used to this but,
it feels freaking good.
Having him makes me thankful for
breathing and waking up every day.
Thank you.
What are these for?
My gifts to you.
This one is for your birthday.
This one is for anniversary.
For monthsary.
For saying thank you.
For saying sorry.
And for saying I love you.
I don't know,
I just wanted to give you a gift.
I'm so happy
that you are part of my life.
Damn you, Palma!
Yeah.
Damn me.
The sunset's so beautiful.
As beautiful as you.
He's getting better at compliments.
I hope it stays this way.
I hope this never ends.
Alys.
If I could only stop
the sun from setting,
hold back time,
I'd do it right now.
Let's just think that
we're escaping from reality somehow.
Are you happy?
Beyond happy.
Everything feels so soothing and
being with you makes me feel
like i made the right decision.
Me too.
Tripp was right.
I still love Drake.
I always did.
I will always do.
They were right.
No matter what happens
when you love a person,
you can't help it.
That's where you'll always end up.
I wish we were always like this.
Seriously?
You actually slept on the couch?
Good night, Drake.
Good night, Drakey Baby.
I’ve waited for this moment.
I wish we could go back to
when we were in high school.
But this time,
we'll make things right.
Alys,
I'm really, really sorry for everything.
I hope you can forgive me
for everything I did wrong.
But Alys, I want you to know
that you're the only one.
Then.
Now.
And until the end.
Only you.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
If I talk to Tripp,
do you promise to stay with me in this?
I promise.
Zy?
Hmm?
Stand by your decision, okay?
People are hurting already.
This is enough.
How is she?
Fier is pregnant.